<resources>
    <string name="lat">"Latitude"</string>
        <string name="lng">"Longitude"</string>
    <string name="location">"Location"</string>
    <string name="aroma_day">"Lunar day Flavor"</string>
    <string name="aroma_url">"http://www.iherb.com/search?kw=#key\u0026rcode=dsr347"</string>
    <string name="buy_discount">Buy with discount</string>
    <string name="extra_sign_url">http://www.irinabass.org/luna-v-znakax-zodiaka-medicinskoe-vliyanie/#sign</string>
    <string name="extra_day_url">http://www.irinabass.org/astropsixologiya/lunnye-dni/eng#day</string>
    <string name="read_more">"Detailed description"</string>
    <string name="from">"From"</string>
    <string name="to">"to"</string>
    <string name="no_data">"There is no information for this time. Try to download the latest version. Recent data "</string>
    <string name="dream1">"Prophetic. Dreams may be prophetic. Be attentive to what you had seen in the dream. It may show you solutions of current difficulties. If it was a bad dream - don't tell it to anyone"</string>
    <string name="dream2">"The signs. Dreams are not informative. High risk of wishful thinking"</string>
    <string name="dream3">"The signs. Dreams are not informative. Don't let yourself be offended even in dreams. If you see flowers - be ready for serious karmic challenge. "</string>
    <string name="dream4">"Prophetic, but comes true not very soon. Hair may be significant"</string>
    <string name="dream5">"The signs. Journey - is a very good sign. Nightmare - hidden disease"</string>
    <string name="dream6">"Prophetic. Don't tell anyone your dreams. Dreams encrypted and are full of symbols"</string>
    <string name="dream7">"Prophetic. Often predictive. Information can be easily decrypted"</string>
    <string name="dream8">"The signs. Indicate the direction you should move. Intricate, understood after it comes true."</string>
    <string name="dream9">"Not informative. Often painful and unpleasant. Try to forget it"</string>
    <string name="dream10">"Not informative. Beautiful and useless dreams. Ancestors may be important"</string>
    <string name="dream11">"Not informative. Pleasant dreams - you are on the right track, but if you bring harm to someone - think about it"</string>
    <string name="dream12">"The signs. Pay attention to pleasant dreams. Nightmares are not informative"</string>
    <string name="dream13">"The signs. Indicate current unsolved problems. The dreams are symbolic"</string>
    <string name="dream14">"The signs. It is difficult to understand. To decrypt help is needed"</string>
    <string name="dream15">"The signs. Very important. Information is encrypted"</string>
    <string name="dream16">"The signs. Purifying dreams. Sick person gets rid of deaseases, healthy - relievs tension"</string>
    <string name="dream17">"The signs. Dreams are significant, how you feel after waiking up is important. If you feel good - you are on the right track, if onerously and not good - you're doing something wrong, review your life positions"</string>
    <string name="dream18">"The signs. You can see obstacles. Try to sleep less today"</string>
    <string name="dream19">"The signs. Dreams can frighten, but will help you to see something new in yourself"</string>
    <string name="dream20">"Prophetic. Brings extremely useful information. You can control dreams and even penetrate into someone's dream"</string>
    <string name="dream21">"Not informative. Quickly forgotten. Don't come true"</string>
    <string name="dream22">"The signs. Very important. They provide answers for current questions"</string>
    <string name="dream23">"The signs. In the dreams stress is relieved. Frightening and painful, but may be important"</string>
    <string name="dream24">"The signs. Reflect the state of your sexual energy. Not details, but the feeling after waiking up is important."</string>
    <string name="dream25">"Prophetic. If you have a bad dream, make sure you spend time in prayers and purification. It may be predictive. "</string>
    <string name="dream26">"Not informative. Reflection of current life"</string>
    <string name="dream27">"The signs. Will help to get rid of illusions. They separate life from fantasies, difficult to interpret "</string>
    <string name="dream28">"The signs. You can see yourself in a new way. Can discover past lives"</string>
    <string name="dream29">"Not informative. Anxious and frightening dreams. Don't come true"</string>
    <string name="dream30">"Prophetic. Bright, joyful and prophetic dreams"</string>
    <string name="dream2901">"Prophetic. Dreams can be prophetic. Be attentive to what you had seen in the dream. It may show you solutions of current difficulties. If it was a bad dream - don't tell it to anyone"</string>
    <string name="dream3001">"Prophetic. Dreams can be prophetic. Be attentive to what you had seen in the dream. It may show you solutions of current difficulties. If it was a bad dream - don't tell it to anyone"</string>
    <string name="dream102">"The signs. Dreams are not informative. High risk of wishful thinking"</string>
    
    <string name="aroma_basil">"Basil. Strong, nice and fresh. Antioxidant, antimicrobial, anti-inflammatory action"</string>
    <string name="aroma_orange">"The orange. Citrus, light, warm, sweet. Protects the psyche. Antidepressant. Aspirations for development, leadership, glory and nobility. Supplements to weight loss"</string>
    <string name="aroma_sandal">"Sandalwood. Not strong, but long-lasting, gentle and exotic. Relieves anxiety and tension. Antiseptic"</string>
    <string name="aroma_lemon">"Lemon. Citrus, fresh, cool. Lowers blood pressure, normalizes digestion, supplements to detoxification and stimulates healing"</string>
    <string name="aroma_gardenia">"Gardenia. Tropical, placidity and lightness. Will help you to maintain mental balance and harmony"</string>
    <string name="aroma_heather">"The Heather. Tart, bitter. Blood purification and diuretic effect. Not recommended during stomch diseases"</string>
    <string name="aroma_orchid">"Orchid. Soothes, relieves mental stress. Treatment from dizziness"</string>
    <string name="aroma_marjoram">"Marjoram. Evening, warm, spicy. Strong bactericidal effect, painkiller. Improves digestion, stimulates blood circulation"</string>
    <string name="aroma_melissa">"Melissa. Fresh, cool, invigorating. Antispasmodic, antiviral, anti-allergic remedy. Improves mood, reduces irritability"</string>
    <string name="aroma_litsea_kubeba">"Litsea cubeba. Strong, sweet, cool. Eliminates asthenic and depressive states, prevents fatigue"</string>
    <string name="aroma_ylang">"Ylang-ylang. Strong, nice, sweet, exotic. Antiseptic, bactericidal effect. Erotic stimulant"</string>
    <string name="aroma_grapefruit">"Grapefruit. Pleasant, tender and little bitter. Antidepressant. Supplements to weight loss. Helps to perceive reality objectively"</string>
    <string name="aroma_neroli">"Neroli. Very pleasant, fresh. Soothing, antiseptic agent. Aphrodisiac"</string>
    <string name="aroma_clove">"Clove. Strong, sharp. The smell of desire and success. Gives success, wealth and prosperity"</string>
    <string name="aroma_camomile">"Chamomile. Sweet-grass, fruity, with slight smell of hay . A calming effect, relieves irritation. Good disinfectant effect"</string>
    <string name="aroma_rosemary">"Rosemary. Strong, fresh, bitter. Eliminates shyness and awkwardness, uncertainty. Helps memorizing, strong aphrodisiac"</string>
    <string name="aroma_incense">"Frankincense. Warm, resinous. Regenerating effect. Eliminates sleeplessness and fears"</string>
    <string name="aroma_rose">"The rose. Sweet, tart, honey. Increases work efficiency. Especially good for women. Love, fertility and healing"</string>
    <string name="aroma_cinnamon">"Cinnamon. Strong, spicy. Warmth, inspiration, creating a homely atmosphere. Creative mood"</string>
    <string name="aroma_cedar">"Cedar. Woody, fresh. Causes aversion to alcohol. Purifies and protects"</string>
    <string name="aroma_lavender">"Lavender. Soft and fresh. Stabilizes the pulse, soothes the pain. Purity and tenderness"</string>
    <string name="aroma_mandarin">"Mandarin. Citrus. Improves mood, encourages. Joy and liveliness"</string>
    <string name="aroma_bay">"Laurel. Woody. Purification effect. Causes appetite and helps digestion"</string>
    <string name="aroma_jasmine">"Jasmine. Sweet. Has a strong sedative effect. The symbol of passionate love"</string>
    <string name="aroma_mirra">"Myrrh. Exquisite. Encourages and relieves emotional stress"</string>
    <string name="information">"Information"</string>
    <string name="next_time">"Not now"</string>
    <string name="ok_no_problem">"Ok. No problem!"</string>
    <string name="add_estimate">"Please rate the app. Thanks for the feedback!"</string>
    <string name="about_day">"About the moon"</string>
    <string name="add_request">"Thank you for using the application. Your opinions and suggestions are very important. Please send feedback flywolf1978@gmail.com"</string>
    <string name="moon_day">"lunar day"</string>
    <string name="simple_description">"To see description tap the image. Use the paging"</string>
    <string name="app_name">"Lunar Calendar PRO"</string>
    <string name="hello_world">"Lunar Calendar"</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">"Settings"</string>
    <string name="quit">"Exit"</string>
    <string name="next">"Next"</string>
    <string name="previous">"Previous"</string>
    <string name="current">"Current"</string>
    <string name="about">"About"</string>
    <string name="day1">"1st lunar day. Lamp. Planning time"</string>
    <string name="day2">"2nd lunar day. Cornucopia. Make gifts"</string>
    <string name="day3">"3rd lunar day. Leopard. Defend your interests"</string>
    <string name="day4">"4th lunar day. Paradise tree. You may face temptations"</string>
    <string name="day5">"5th lunar day. Unicorn. Express yourself actively"</string>
    <string name="day6">"6th lunar day. The bird. Privacy, intuition is acute"</string>
    <string name="day7">"7th lunar day. Windrose. Provocations, it is dangerous to lie"</string>
    <string name="day8">"8th lunar day. Fire. Day of repentance and purification"</string>
    <string name="day9">"9th lunar day. The bat. Anxieties, illusions and bad news. Bad (satanic) day"</string>
    <string name="day10">"10th lunar day. Fountain. Active rest, good to start construction of the house"</string>
    <string name="day11">"11th lunar day. The crown. Strong energy, be careful"</string>
    <string name="day12">"12th lunar day. The heart. Show mercy and compassion"</string>
    <string name="day13">"13th lunar day. The ring. Take care of yourself, it is easy to free yourself from the burden of the past. Good day"</string>
    <string name="day14">"14th lunar day. The pipe. Good for new undertakings, less liquids. Good day"</string>
    <string name="day15">"15th lunar day. The snake. Temptations, the control is weakened. Bad(satanic) day"</string>
    <string name="day16">"16th lunar day. The dove. Bright and harmonious day"</string>
    <string name="day17">"17th lunar day. The bunch of grapes. A day of fun and love. Good day"</string>
    <string name="day18">"18th lunar day. Mirror. Everything you hear about yourself is truth"</string>
    <string name="day19">"19th lunar day. The spider. Vampires' day, don't get caught up in the spiderweb. Bad(satanic) day"</string>
    <string name="day20">"20th lunar day. The eagle. Day of the victory over yourself, go for it!"</string>
    <string name="day21">"21st lunar day. Rhe horse. Records and achievements, new work"</string>
    <string name="day22">"22nd lunar day. The elephant. Day of wisdom. Good day"</string>
    <string name="day23">"23rd day of the moon. The crocodile. Aggression and violence, be careful"</string>
    <string name="day24">"24th lunar day. The bear. The Foundation of new businesses, activness"</string>
    <string name="day25">"25th lunar day. The turtle. Passivity and deliberation"</string>
    <string name="day26">"26th lunar day. The toad. Do not swear, avoid spendings. Bad(satanic) day"</string>
    <string name="day27">"27th lunar day. Trident. Intuition and discoveries, water procedures, be careful in outdoor water"</string>
    <string name="day28">"28th lunar day. The Lotus. Day of insights and transformation. Good day"</string>
    <string name="day29">"29th lunar day. Octopus. Dangerous day, be responsible. Bad(satanic) day"</string>
    <string name="day30">"30th lunar day. The golden swan. Day of love, forgiveness, repentance and summerizing"</string>
    <string name="day2901">"29/1st lunar day. Octopus, lamp"</string>
    <string name="day3001">"30/1st lunar day. Golden swan, lamp"</string>
    <string name="day102">"1/2nd lunar day. Lamp, cornucopia"</string>
    <string name="no_description">"No description"</string>
    <string name="aries">"Aries. The propensity to conflict, excessive impulsiveness. Possible to resolve old problems with no effort"</string>
    <string name="taurus">"Taurus. Calm, slow response. Household activity, repairment. Avoid significant deals"</string>
    <string name="gemini">"Twins. Activities and suggestibility. Unnecessary actions. Well to be on the road"</string>
    <string name="cancer">"Cancer. Sensitivity, getting deep into yourself. Time to create comfort"</string>
    <string name="leo">"Lion. Cheerfulness. Make compliments. Have fun and take care of the appearance. Presentations are successful"</string>
    <string name="virgo">"Virgo. Practicality and preciseness
. Do not make important decisions. Good to do monotonous work"</string>
    <string name="libra">"Libra. Peace and harmony. Good to make peace. It is difficult to make a choice. Diplomacy is successful"</string>
    <string name="scorpio">"Scorpio. The excitement and passion. Sensitivity increases. Do not take any drastic action"</string>
    <string name="sagittarius">"Sagittarius. Order and stability. The time to teach and to learn"</string>
    <string name="capricorn">"Capricorn. Duties and responsibilities. The sensitivity is low. Logic prevails"</string>
    <string name="aquarius">"Aquarius. Freedom and emancipation. Emotions take over. Reforms and experiments. Players are lucky"</string>
    <string name="pisces">"Fish. Romance and daydreaming. Aesthetic experience. Deep feelings"</string>
    <string name="GROW">"Waxing moon"</string>
    <string name="WANNING">"Waning moon"</string>
    <string name="FULL">"Full moon"</string>
    <string name="NEW">"New moon"</string>
    <string name="day_symbol">"Symbol of the day"</string>
    <string name="salt">"Classical element of the Earth. Spoil yourself with something salty"</string>
    <string name="proteins">"Classical element of the Fire. Useful protein food"</string>
    <string name="fats">"Classical element of the Air. Fatty foods are well absorbed"</string>
    <string name="carbohydrates">"Classical element of the Water. Carbohydrates are well absorbed"</string>
    <string name="growsalat">"Waxing Moon and the classical element of the Water. Good to plant leafy vegetables"</string>
    <string name="growflower">"Waxing Moon and classical element of the Air. You can plant flowers"</string>
    <string name="growtomato">"Waxing Moon and classical element of the Fire. Good to plant cucumbers and tomatoes"</string>
    <string name="growpotato">"Waning Moon and classical element of the Earth. Good to plant rooted plants"</string>
    <string name="aries_body">"Aries (opposit Libra). Vulnerable head. Kidneys are least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="taurus_body">"Taurus(opposit Scorpio). Vulnerable throat. Genitals and rectum are the least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="gemini_body">"Gemini(opposit Sagittarius). Vulnerable langs. Blood, hips, liver least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="cancer_body">"Cancer(opposit Capricorn). Vulnerable stomach. Skin, bones, biliary least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="leo_body">"Leo(opposit Aquarius). Vulnerable heart. Legs, nervs the least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="virgo_body">"Virgo(opposit Pisces). Vulnerable intestine. Feet least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="libra_body">"Libra(opposit Aries). Kidneys are vulnerable. The head is the least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="scorpio_body">"Scorpio(opposit Taurus). Vulnerable genitals and rectum. Throat is the least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="sagittarius_body">"Sagittarius(opposite Twins). Vulnerable blood, hips, liver . Langs are the least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="capricorn_body">"Capricorn(opposit Cancer). Vulnerable skin, bones, biliary. The stomach is the least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="aquarius_body">"Aquarius(opposite Lion). Feet and nervs are vulnerable. Heart is the least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="pisces_body">"Pisces (oppositi Virgo). Vulnerable feet. The intestine is the least sensitive"</string>
    <string name="haircut">"Good time to have a haircut"</string>
    <string name="haircut_not">"Haircut is not recommended"</string>
    <string name="manwomen">"Auspicious day for relations"</string>
    <string name="manwomen_not">"It is better to avoid intimacy"</string>
    <string name="manwomen_not_scorpio">"Moon in Scorpio. Genitals are sensitive. High risk of infection. On the other hand, the brightest feelings possible to get on this day ;)"</string>
    <string name="clear">"Cleaning and purification procedures are recommended"</string>
    <string name="shower">"Water procedures are useful"</string>
    <string name="shower_not">"Water procedures are not recommended"</string>
    <string name="good">"Good lunar day"</string>
    <string name="bad">"Negative (satanic) lunar day"</string>
    <string name="muladhara_fill">"Muladhara. Repletion"</string>
    <string name="muladhara_realize">"Muladhara. Expression"</string>
    <string name="svadhistana_fill">"Svadhishthana. Repletion"</string>
    <string name="svadhistana_realize">"Svadhishthana. Expression"</string>
    <string name="manipura_fill">"Manipur. Repletion"</string>
    <string name="manipura_realize">"Manipur. Expression"</string>
    <string name="anahata_fill">"Anahata. Repletion
"</string>
    <string name="anahata_realize">"Anahata. Expression"</string>
    <string name="vishudha_fill">"Vishuddha. Repletion
"</string>
    <string name="vishudha_realize">"Vishuddha. Expression"</string>
    <string name="adgana_fill">"Ajna. Repletion
"</string>
    <string name="adgana_realize">"Ajna. Expression"</string>
    <string name="sahasrara_fill">"Sahasrara. Repletion
"</string>
    <string name="sahasrara_realize">"Sahasrara. Expression"</string>

    <string-array name="languages">
        <item>"Select language"</item>
        <item>"Russian "</item>
        <item>"English"</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>